

# **POURIYA SEDAGHAT**

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT

- +98 9389372901
- □ pouriyask1@gmail.com
- Iran, Tehran

#### **EDUCATION**

# 2018 - 2023 ISLAMIC AZAD UNIVERSITY, SOUTH TEHRAN BRANCH

 Bachelor of Electrical Engineering majoring in electricity

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Tailwind CSS
- Sass
- Javascript
- Jquery
- Ajax
- Typescript
- React js
- Next is
- · Jest js and pupeteer
- State Managment
- MongoDB Database

#### **PROFILE**

I am a Frontend developer with experience and skill in web design and UI/UX development.

With high ability in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Sass, JavaScript, Jquery, Ajax, Typescript, Reactjs, Nextjs, State Manegments, Mongodb Database and..., I can create dynamic and attractive user interface.

In addition, by using popular JavaScript libraries and frameworks such as Reactjs and Nextjs and JavaScript packages, I have been able to develop projects with high speed and quality.

The ability to communicate effectively with the team as well as the ability to solve complex problems are also among my other characteristics.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Arya Route Processing Company

2023 - 2024

Frontend Developer

- Front-end developer in software development team
- Optimizing JavaScript codes and using modern frameworks such as Reactjs and Nextjs
- Designing and implementing a visual user interface based on existing designs
- Ability to achieve project timelines and deliver on time
- Participating in user needs analysis sessions and accepting user interface feedback
- Creating a responsive and beautiful user interface to improve the user experience
- · Collaborate with different teams to meet project needs and goals
- ..

## Tech Green Solution ca

2023 - 2023

Frontend Developer

- Tech Green Solutions web application development with Next js V-12
- Development of all parts of the application

#### Skills:

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English (intermediate)
- Persian (Fluent)

#### **SOCILA NETWORK**

- Github
- Stackoverflow
- LinkedIn
- X (Twitter)
- Whatsapp
- Telegram

## **REPOSITORIES**

- Tech Green Solutions
- Fullstack Shopping (app router)
- Fullstack Shopping (page router)
- Shopping Cart

- Sass
- Next js (page router)
- MongoDB Database
- Node js

## Packages:

- sass
- bootstrap
- reactstrap
- · react-cookie
- sweetalert2
- react-hook-form
- mongoose ( MongoDB Driver For Node js )
- next-auth

#### Front Cast

2023 - 2023

# Web Application Developer

- Fullstack Shopping web application development with Next js V-14
- Development of all parts of the application

# Skills:

- HTML
- CSS
- Tailwind CSS
- Sass
- Typescript
- Nextjs (app router and page router)
- MongoDB Database
- Node js
- State Managment (context)

## Packages:

- sass
- @headlessui/react
- js-cookie
- react-toastify

- react-hook-form
- mongoose (MongoDB Driver For Nodejs)
- next-auth

## **Front Cast**

2023 - 2023

Web Application Developer

- Shopping Cart web application development with React js
- Only the front part of the application has been developed

#### Skills:

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Sass
- Typescript
- Reactjs
- State Managment ( Redux Toolkit )

# Packages:

- sass
- bootstrap
- react-bootstrap
- @reduxjs/toolkit
- react-redux
- js-cookie
- react-toastify
- react-hook-form